<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Orchestral on Mathew A. Kramer</title>
    <link>https://mathewkramer.io/categories/orchestral/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Orchestral on Mathew A. Kramer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mathewkramer.io/categories/orchestral/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TGDNE series (2/?): Are you sure this spaceship is abandoned?</title>
      <link>https://mathewkramer.io/2022/220428_spaceship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathewkramer.io/2022/220428_spaceship/</guid>
      <description>This is the second track in my &amp;ldquo;This Game Does Not Exist&amp;rdquo; collection, and also the first of my &amp;ldquo;morning sprints&amp;rdquo;, where I try to spend an hour in the morning developing some new idea. Of course, the polishing took longer than an hour, but all in all, this is more of a proof-of-concept than what I would call a full-fledged track: A quick idea to get something out there (which is what matters)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGDNE series (1/?): Oops! You found the forest boss</title>
      <link>https://mathewkramer.io/2022/220425_forestboss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathewkramer.io/2022/220425_forestboss/</guid>
      <description>This was orignally meant to be my submission for a course on video game music I took on the side this semester. I ended up getting to do a collaboration with a great dev team and produce music for an actual game, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to abandon this one. So, it gets to be the first entry in my &amp;ldquo;This Game Does Not Exist&amp;rdquo; collection of game-inspired but as yet un-play-tested music!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Splotch Gallery OST now on Bandcamp and SoundCloud!</title>
      <link>https://mathewkramer.io/2022/220419_nosplotch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathewkramer.io/2022/220419_nosplotch/</guid>
      <description>This (mini- (mini-)) mini-album is the result of a collaboration with NoShotStudios, who developed the puzzle platformer No Splotch Gallery. Check out the game!
The developers asked for a couple of classical-inspired tracks to fit the museum gallery setting, and they turned out to be really fun to make! You can listen below.
Bandcamp No Splotch Gallery (Original Soundtrack) by mathew SoundCloud mathew · No Splotch Gallery (Original Soundtrack) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
